Rapport !
The Duke of England brought men
and surrounds the general's residence.
He asks the general to release his daughter.
He wants to see her alive
or see her body if she is dead.
Quoi ?
He still dares to come here!
NOW,
it's time to test
our acting skills.
Where is Wan'er?
I want to see her.
Father-in-law,
you bring so many people to check on me?
It's too kind.
Ning Yuanci!
My daughter just entered your home yesterday,
and today she almost perished in the flames.
You want
Lock him up or what?
Calm down.
I'm not stopping you from seeing it.
The simple wish of an old father,
I will definitely satisfy him.
Wan'er!
Father-in-law.
Okay, but
no violence!
Wan'er,
what exactly happened last night?
Did Ning Yuanci try to kill you?
Last night there was a sudden fire in the residence.
It's the general
who risked his life to save me.
How could he hurt me?
Since the cause of the fire
in the general's residence is not yet established,
Wan'er,
I'll take you home first.
Don't even think about it!
Ning Yuanci,
do you want to imprison my daughter?
Since Xue Ruowan is my wife,
It’s naturally up to me to protect her.
Father-in-law,
you better worry
of your youngest.
Last night someone saw it with their own eyes
discreetly infiltrate my general residence
and set fire.
Anything !
How could Ying'er do such a thing?
Out of love, quite simply.
If not, why else?
It wouldn't be the duke who sent someone
set fire to my residence?
Toi...
Monsieur le Duc, it’s terrible!
The second lady has disappeared!
Quoi ?
Xue Keying,
Wouldn't she have run away for fear of being punished?
Wait until I find Ying'er to clarify this,
and I will come back to settle my accounts with you!
Wan'er,
take care of yourself,
Don't forget your father's recommendations.
Be well, father-in-law.
Pay attention to the steps.
Looks like my acting
was rather convincing,
I got that old fox.
I mean,
this feint from earlier
surely destabilized Xue Shiyan.
It must be
completely lost,
he absolutely doesn't know
what I'm going to do.
He must know that the poisoning failed
and that the assassin did not succeed either,
that's why he came to test you with excuses.
Even if we've impressed him so far,
the fact that Xue Keying
either in your residence
can't stay secret for long.
He's not going to stop there.
No problem.
We face every attack,
we adapt to each situation.
Now I know
that he pretends to be weak to hit better,
but he doesn't know yet
how many faces I have.
I'm going to think carefully about a strategy
to unmask his true face.
Our marriage,
and if we...
I know,
you probably don't want to be involved
to this power struggle.
We didn't do the ceremony,
nor consummated the marriage,
it's not a real marriage.
I will write to you
a divorce letter right away.
I hope that the general
will continue to play the role of my husband.
Um, that's not a good idea.
We're not even a real couple.
And then,
this kind of contractual marriage,
I've never played this with a woman.
Keying isn't awake yet,
I can't abandon it.
Moreover,
I see clearly that General Ning
sincerely love him.
Since we
we have a common enemy,
we should ally
to quickly find
Xue Shiyan's evidence of betrayal.
This painting of the reborn phoenix
left to me by my mother
before his death.
She was partially
destroyed by fire.
I wanted to have it restored first,
but thinking about it,
the phoenix is ​​reborn from the flames.
So I asked Mr. Chu
to paint me a new one.
It's this one.
This deer-shaped totem,
it was already there originally.
Oui.
The burned part,
This is precisely where the totem was located.
I described to Mr. Chu
the general style,
and he reproduced it.
But the original work
est de Xue Shiyan.
Did he paint it?
During her lifetime, my mother
admired my father's talent.
Even his failed drafts,
she considered them treasures.
That day, Xiao Lan
probably wanted to help me
to restore this painting.
But in the end...
The general found on the spy of the Northern Kingdom
this painting of the princess for the wedding of peace
and the original painting of the reborn Phoenix,
they are actually
with the same hand.
But looking carefully,
we discover that
the one copied by Mr. Chu
does not have the same brush stroke as the original.
So that proves well
that the duke is suspected of collusion with the enemy.
Just stop him and question him
directly, right?
The original was destroyed,
the spy refuses to speak,
with only this paint,
it will be difficult to condemn the duke.
Unless you make the snake come out of its hole,
the best thing is to catch them in the act.
I see.
My general,
Mr. Chu is truly innocent,
Please release him.
Moreover,
his painting art is much better than mine.
Maybe
can he help us find
more clues.
Exactly !
What about the male protagonist then?
How could we forget it?
No matter how you question me,
I will never plead guilty.
Mr. Chu.
Little sister Wan.
NOW,
I should rather call you Madam General.
Mr Chu,
It was I who was wrong towards you.
I was unable to testify on your behalf.
Make you endure this prison suffering.
No, no, no.
It doesn't concern you.
These little sufferings,
I can handle them.
La main de Chu Qingyun va bien.
I knew he wasn't completely dead.
Ah, you then, Ning Yuanci!
You just wanted to scare me.
On this painting of the princess's wedding,
do you notice anything strange?
It seems that...
And the painting left by your mother
use the same canvas.
When I repainted the Phoenix Reborn,
as I didn't find
exactly the same canvas,
I had to use rice paper instead.
This painting is very rare,
the material is very particular,
that's why I remember it.
And apart from that?
I don't see anything else.
General Ning,
do you really want to let me out?
Stop chatting.
But recently, dark currents are shaking the city.
I fear it will be more dangerous for you outside.
You don't want to consider
to reside temporarily at the general's residence?
May Ning Yuanci want to free me
does not mean that I will put myself at his service.
He and I are not on the same side.
Little sister Wan,
you married this guy
of a man with obscure intentions.
You absolutely must protect yourself.
So you too, be careful.
Did you see?
I let him go
and he says bad things about me behind my back.
If General Ning intends to let him go,
why doesn't he come out
to tell him to his face?
There, you don't understand.
If I had come in person,
how could he
confess everything so easily?
Didn't you hear what he said earlier?
He and I are not the same type.
What is it called?
The men's competition.
Similars repel each other,
opposites attract.
You don't understand that?
This time I'm so smooth
that I slip into the role of Ning Yuanci.
You quickly get into character.
YOU,
surround the general's residence
like an impenetrable fortress.
Everyone
enters and leaves with a portrait.
Those who don't have a portrait,
no passage authorized.
If you still let thieves sneak in,
I will punish you.
I will send you to build walls on the border.
So like that, to be a great general,
it's so enjoyable.
It's just playing
a dark, crazy and tyrannical CEO,
what's difficult?
Are you talking or not?
Who gave you this portrait?
Who is your superior?
Bah !
Are you talking or not?
Do you want to cut off my other hand?
The swords for playing are all wrong,
I don't need to really kill.
Come on, hit me,
cut my neck.
You go-y.
You're not supposed to kneel and beg
then reveal to me
the whole truth?
How does a simple extra
can play so righteously
and intensity?
I really need to accept less
of those stupid idol dramas.
Power intrigues,
I feel like my brain isn't keeping up.
General,
the servant who attempted the assassination last night,
after autopsy,
it was a woman disguised as a man.
His face
has already been drawn by your subordinate.
So it's a woman.
She looks familiar to me.
Where did I see her?
Toi,
go get all the servants in the residence
and bring them into my courtyard,
I'm going to question them.
But general,
shouldn't they stay away?
And.
But women have a keen eye and a subtle mind.
All suspicious movements,
They know them better than you.
So I'm going.
Go quickly.
Quickly, quickly, quickly.
Are you talking or not?
I've seen you before.
You wouldn't have given Ning
You brought me a night meal.
General,
I don't dare.
I never had such a thought.
Wh...what are you doing?
I have no other intention.
I just want you to watch,
have you ever seen
this person in the portrait?
Moi,
I think I saw her
at the Jinming Lake engagement banquet.
Give me that.
It is also for his own good.
Ning Yuanci wants to take the young lady
as hostage
to threaten the Duke's manor.
You don't want her to get hurt, do you?
This medicine for miss's body,
It’s safe, right?
If she takes it, she will just have a little discomfort.
At that moment, you will persist in saying
that it was Ning Yuanci who did this.
Don't forget,
the life of your whole family
is in whose hands.
Be wise.
You saw well.
It's all true,
I wouldn't dare lie.